[{"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Where were the Boer Republics located?", "correct_answer": "Across South Africa", "incorrect_answers": ["In the Netherlands", "They were early Puritan settlements in the eastern North America", "Minor British isles"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Mars has two natural satellites. What are their names?", "correct_answer": "Phobos and Deimos", "incorrect_answers": ["Vulcan and Apollo", "Tom and Jerry", "Zeus and Hara"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "All of the dinosaurs in the blockbuster film Jurassic Park were created by computer animation.", "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "In a list of numbers what, is the mode?", "correct_answer": "The number seen most frequently", "incorrect_answers": ["The number of items in the list", "The biggest number minus the smallest number", "The middle number"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Whose face appears at the very end of the film, after the credits roll?", "correct_answer": "Rick Chance", "incorrect_answers": ["Eric Masters", "Ruth Lanier", "Jimmy Harts"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "This director/writer/producer/actress was married to writer Dan Greenburgand and journalist Carl Bernstein. In 1987 she married her third husband, Nicholas Pileggi.", "correct_answer": "Nora Ephron", "incorrect_answers": ["Lee Grant", "Melanie Mayron", "Betty Kaplan"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Mammals lived alongside dinosaurs.", "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What actor won an Academy Award in 1980 for portraying a character who loved the smell of napalm in the morning?", "correct_answer": "Robert Duvall", "incorrect_answers": ["Robert Redford", "Robert De Niro", "Robert Young"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "In The Lord of the Rings, what are the Dark Lord Saurons chief henchmen called?", "correct_answer": "Nazgul", "incorrect_answers": ["Dragons", "Balrogs", "Orcs"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "There are two classes of starfish. Name them.", "correct_answer": "Sea Star and Brittle Stars", "incorrect_answers": ["Salt Stars and Fresh Stars", "Soft Stars and Hard Stars", "Common Stars and Rare Stars"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Which wedding anniversary is celebrated internationally as the Diamond Wedding Anniversary, or Diamond Wedding Day?", "correct_answer": "60th anniversary", "incorrect_answers": ["80th anniversary", "50th anniversary", "40th anniversary"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "This country is not a federal republic.", "correct_answer": "Laos", "incorrect_answers": ["Austria", "Ethiopia", "Pakistan"]}]